Finding Aid for Camp Al-Gon-Quian (Burt Lake, Mich.) records, 1925-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Campers files 1925-1967
  - Chronological 1925-1967
    - 1957
      - Fahrner, Jackie
      - Flintermann, Andy
      - Glanz, Rick
      - Gould, Bruce F.
      - Hall, Thomas James Jr. "Tommy"
      - Healy, Charles Edw.
      - Holt, Jack
      - Hopewell, Stanley John (Stan)
      - Horste, David
      - Johnson, Paul E. "Pej"
      - Jones, Jeff
      - Kelly, Lark
      - Keyser, William Earl "Bill" (includes Bruce Hartley "Boop")
      - Lamb, Robert Jeffrey (Jeff) (Box 19)
      - Lathers, John Robert (Johnny)
      - Leland, Joshua (Josh)
      - Leonelli, Lance
      - Lohr, Bill
      - Loop, Chris
      - Mackey, Walter Jay (Rusty)
      - Malcolm, John Putnam (Johnny)
      - McCullough, Bill
      - McKee, Philip Leopold (Phil)
      - Olson, Lance (includes Nels & Christopher Scott "Chris") (1957-1961)
      - Ostermann, Hal
      - Peckinpaugh, Peck
      - Rabinovitch, Mark
      - Rickard, Robert Raleigh "Robbie"
      - Rider, Pete
      - Robinson, Burnett
      - Ross, Bob
      - Shaeffer, Leland Dale
      - Sheasby, John Jimmy (includes John Frederick)
      - Spitzley, Jim
      - Teeple, Ross Jr. "Junior"
      - Weber, Mark
      - Weintraub, Gary D.
      - White, Dave
      - Yax, Gerry
    - 1958
      [Restricted until January 1 2058 ]
      - Achterhoff, Bobby (Box 19)
      - Barbour, Thomas Chittenden "Tommy"
      - Barrows, Frank Clifford (includes Peter B.) (1958-1961)
      - Bentlage, Roger Eric "Rog"
      - Bernstein, Robert Boyd "Bob"
      - Bradshaw, James Lloyd "Jimmy"
      - Brown, Henry Pell Jr. "Pell" (includes Kent Masterson "Kenny") (1958-1959)
      - Brett, Bradford Arnold "Skip"
      - Bunday, John Frederick
      - Bursley, Philip Everette
      - Caveny, Christopher "Chris"
      - Davison, Fent
      - Faye, Leslie Eitig "Lee"
      - Foote, Robert L. "Robbie"
      - Ford, Frederick Brier "Ricky" (includes Robert Ernest "Robby"
      - Franklin, James Lincoln "Jim"
      - Geier, Frederick Wurlitzer "Fritz"
      - Hall, Carter Wilkinson "Terry"
      - Heavenrich, Max Philip
      - Hendee, Richmond Shreve "Ric" (includes Steven Hunter "Stebo")
      - Holley, David Cullen
      - Holley, George M. III
      - Hord, Thomas Doggett "Tom"
      - Husted, Clark Edgell
      - King, Robert Lee "Bob"
      - Klopfenstein, Charles Edward "Chuck"
      - Knoop, Rudolph Wurlitzer "Roddy"
      - Kowalk, Lawrence Carl "Larry"
      - Lathrop, Henry Krike
      - Lee, Roger William "Roge"
      - Marks, Standish Backus "Sandy"
      - Matthews, Calvin Carl "Cal"
      - Maxon, Philip Nelson "Phil"
      - May, Thomas P. "Tom"
      - McCammon, William Gavin "Bill"
      - Moen, James C. "Jimmie"
      - Morris, Richard Risdon "Rick"
      - Myers, Craig Alan
      - Pittman, Steuart (includes John) (1955-1958)
      - Raisbeck, John Wallace "Johnny"
      - Read, Michael B. "Mokey" (includes Timothy Byrne "Timmy" (1958-1960)
      - Schaefer, Edward Norman "Ted" (includes Henry Frederick "Fritz")
      - Schiff, Charles Louis "Chuck"
      - Smith, Peter Walldorff "Rusty"
      - Spalding, Lyman A.
      - Stahl, James Philip
      - Steiert, Stephen Edward "Steve"
      - Storrs, Albert Miller "Burr"
      - Surdam, Peter Buhl "Pete"
      - Teysen, Kenneth Duane "Kenny" (includes Gregory John) (1958-1964)
      - Weiss, Paul Edward (includes Mark Charles) (1958-1959)
      - Williams, Henry P. "Phil"
      - Woodruff, Michael L. (Mike)
      - Wottrich, Rick
      - Wrigley, George Alexander
    - 1959
      [Restricted until January 1 2059 ]
      - Allan, Harper Keys "Keys" (Box 20)
      - Baldwin, Craig B.
      - Casterline, Ray J. "Butch"
      - Coale, John B. (includes George)
      - Davis, Charles William "Bill" (includes Michael L.)
      - Freedman, Joe Selin
      - Fuger, Tony
      - Green, Daniel Alien "Danny"
      - Halligan, Robert Fletcher "Bobby" (includes Thomas Michael "Tom") (1959-1965)
      - Keenan, Frederick B. "Fred" or "Fritz"
      - Keller, Howard Joseph "Howdy"
      - Kirsch, Christopher John
      - Loftis, Charles B. Jr. "Chuck"
      - Mac Cutcheon, Samuel
      - McCarthy, Tom
      - McCray, Christopher B. "Kit or "Chris"
      - McKay, George (includes Tad)
      - Morrow, David Vincent "Davy"
      - Morsey, Chase III "Chip"
      - Peet, George Millis
      - Reade, W. Kent
      - Risdon, Joseph Edward "Joe"
      - Roach, Philip "Phil"
      - Runciman, Dave
      - Schorger, John Rodger "Jock"
      - Smith, Randall Clayton "Randy"
      - Stadelman, Kris R.
      - Taylor, Hall
      - Turner, George Loomis "Geo"
      - Van Gelder, Cornelius "Neil"
      - Vry, John Lawrence
      - Weislow, Thomas G. "Tommy"
      - West, William J. Jr. (includes Douglas H.)
      - Willimott, John Thomas
      - Young, William T., Jr. "Bill"
    - 1960
      [Restricted until January 1 2060 ]
      - Arnspiger, Richard Jr. "Dicky" (Box 20)
      - Beatty, Robert D., III "Robbie"
      - Bohmer, Charles Christopher "Chris"
      - Bracken, William McKnight "Will"
      - Carman, Steven "Steve"
      - Cassidy, William A. "Bill"
      - Chickering, William Elbridge, III "Bill"
      - Combs, James Arnold "Jimmy"
      - Copi, Thomas Russell "Tom"
      - Coyle, Stephen J. "Steve"
      - Daugherty, James E. "Jim"
      - Davison, Edward Benson "Ed"
      - Dondanville, Michael Pierre
      - Duboff, David Louis "Dave"
      - Ford, John Battice, IV "Johnny"
      - Gilson, Kenneth Arden "Kenny"
      - Girkins, Kent Harrison (Staff)
      - Glancy, Terrance Alfred "Terry" (Includes Michael McCoy & Peter S.)
      - Heaphy, Robert Thomas "Bobby"
      - Hill, Michael Daley
      - Kaatz, William "Bill"
      - Klein, Charles E. "Chad" or "Chuck" (includes Mark L.)
      - Kollar, John Anton (includes James Anthony & Robert Jeff) (1960-1964)
      - Lennox, John Franklin "Johnny"
      - Nusbaum, Howard Phelps "Howey"
      - Potter, Rex Beresford "Berry"
      - Power, Thomas Goodrich "Tom"
      - Scharbat, Joseph Russell "Joe"
      - Schlechte, John Vincent
      - Schorling, William Harrison "Bill"
      - Sibley, Frederick Merrill, III "Freddie"
      - Smoke, Robert Donald "Bob" (includes Paul John) (1960-1961)
      - Stone, Keith S.
      - Stopher, Robert "Bob"
      - Takesh, Farokh J.
      - Temple, William Abbott "Bill"
      - Wiggins, Christopher "Chris"
      - Williams, Ross Wood "Rossie"
      - Zayti, James Jay "Jim"
    - 1961
      [Restricted until January 1 2061 ]
      - Aikens, Allen (Box 21)
      - Bracken, Alexander Elliott "Sandy"
      - Brescia, Donald (includes Robert John) (1961-1963)
      - Chabut, David George "Dave"
      - Coleman, Thomas "Kelley"
      - Cordell, Thomas Frank "Tom"
      - Edwards, Thomas James "Tom"
      - Fairweather, Peter
      - Foster, Douglas R. "Doug"
      - Gabele, Robert
      - George, Thomas M. "Tom"
      - Hallbertg, Lawrence Curtis
      - Ingersoll, Jon (includes Robert) (1961-1962)
      - Inwood, Jeffrey Jerome "Jeff"
      - Johnson, Jerome Ford "Jory"
      - Johnston, C. Gilman "Johnny"
      - Kaye, Thomas
      - Koch, John Joseph (includes Freddie) (1953-1961)
      - May, Thomas "Tom"
      - Messler, Joseph D. "Dyke"
      - Murphy, James
      - Parke, Charles Christopher "Charlie"
      - Pemberton, John Linley "Jody"
      - Planteroth, John Raymond
      - Porter, Allen Ramsey (includes Donald W. "Don") (1961-1962)
      - Post, Timothy "Tim"
      - Reynolds, Thomas A. "Tom"
      - Rhodes, Charles Dover "Charlie"
      - Ries, Granner Strong "Gran"
      - Ringley, Michael John "Mike" (includes Earl Robert "Robby")
      - Ruckelshaus, Thomas F. "Tommy"
      - Saddler, Robert Laurence "Bob"
      - Schultz, Richard
      - Schuster, Donald Edward "Don"
      - Stranahan, Duane
      - Test, Donald N. "Don" (includes Henry Bryant, William Perryman) (1961-1962)
      - Veras, George "Georgie"
      - Wells, Peter Carleton "Pete"
      - Wolf, Mark Marmon (includes Edward Joseph III, Frank Hoke, Fred Hoke) (1961-1964)
      - Young, William Joseph III "Billy"
    - 1962
      [Restricted until January 1 2062 ]
      - Atkins, Thomas Pearce (Box 21)
      - Bartlett, Robert William "Bart" or "Bob"
      - Battin, Richard Lemoine "Dick"
      - Bauer, John Thos. "Johnny"
      - Boyd, Benjamin Fay "Benny"
      - Bursley, Philip E.
      - Coffman, Harold Stephen "Hal"
      - Daniels, Jon F.
      - DeLong, Daniel Roger "Roger"
      - Denise, David James "Dave"
      - Devereaux, Gordon William
      - Donnelly, William J. "Bill" (includes R. George) (1962-1964)
      - DuPerow, Donald Eugene "Don"
      - Durastanti, Dominic (includes Frank)
      - Eder, Jay
      - Failey, John Noel
      - Fogg, Daniel Thos. "Danny"
      - Garmahusen, John Maxwell
      - Gillespie, Lawrence Wm. "Larry"
      - Glossop, Michael Morgan "Mike"
      - Gordon, James Adams
      - Hall, Ben "Benjie"
      - Harper, Stephen Elliot
      - Hellman, Peter Stuart (includes John Alburn "Jack")
      - Hewitt, Jeffrey Lynn
      - Hills, James Crawford "Buff" (includes David & Peter) (1962-1966)
      - Hull, Roger Wolcott "Rog"
      - Ingersoll, Robert Mason "Bob"
      - Kaufmann, Jeffrey Louis "Jeff"
      - Keithley, Joseph Pearce (includes Roy Faber) (1962-1966)
      - Kern, Otto
      - Leinbach, Eric Thomas
      - Magee, Robert "Bobby" (includes Benjamin Rush "Rusty", Kenneth Wendell "Ken", James Lyndon "Jim") (1962-1966)
      - Myers, Philip Everett "Flip"
      - Nardizzi, Mario Len
      - Neville, Thomas Brown "Tom"
      - Offield, James Sanford "Jim"
      - Ostermann, G. Curtis
      - Redeker, John Elliott
      - Reuter, James M.
      - Robinson, Frederick James
      - Robinson, Jefferson D. "Jeff"
      - Robinson, Michael Thomas
      - Rockwell, Francis William "Bill" (includes Thomas Reardon "Tommy" (Box 22)
      - Savage, Frank Albert
      - Snyder, Thomas Earl "Tom"
      - Tenney, Earl Wallace "Buzzy"
      - Tuttle, Leigh Dexter "Dek"
      - Viger, Peter Edward
      - Watson, Gregory James "Greg"
    - 1963
      [Restricted until January 1 2063 ]
      - Albert, Tommy Russell "Buckshot" (Box 22)
      - Altmansberger, David Christian "Chris"
      - Andreae, Stephen Holden "Steve"
      - Atterbury, Harry Leigman
      - Bayer, Thomas Walter "Tom"
      - Blain, Bruce Scott Murray
      - Boeschenstein, William W. Jr. "Bill"
      - Buhrman, Jeffrey Peter "Jeff"
      - Carron, David F.
      - Chickering, John Edw. "Johnny"
      - Cobb, Timothy Jon "Tim"
      - Contrada, Michael Gray "Mike" (includes Charles Vincent)
      - Cool, William Haver "Bill"
      - Coulter, Robert Frederick
      - Davenport, Bruce Talmon Jr.
      - Doucette, William H. "Bill"
      - English, Jeffrey Shaw
      - Ford, Frederick Clifford "Freddy"
      - Gray, William Schuyler "Bill" Jr.
      - Harbaugh, Jack Eugene
      - Heckenkamp, William James "Bill"
      - Henle, John (includes James "Jim") (1963-1966)
      - Hersey, Randolph "Randy"
      - Higbie, Carlton Milo "CM" (includes Harry Quinn)
      - Hobson, David Brian "Davie"
      - Hudson, Joseph Lowthian "Fourie"
      - Iglehart, Austin Scott
      - Kline, James Peirsol (includes William Lacey)
      - Knight, John Lamberson "Johnny"
      - Kretzschmar, William A. "Bill"
      - Kudner, John McKone
      - Kyprie, Paul Marco
      - Lent, John DeWitt (includes William G. "Bill") (1966-1967)
      - Mac Nichol, David Carter "Carter"
      - Marshall, Geoffrey S.
      - Matthews, John Michael (includes Darwin Crawford "Dar")
      - McKinley, John R. III
      - McKone, William Page "Bill"
      - Merritt, Thomas Elliott "Tom"
      - Monro, Michael Alan "Mike"
      - Morris, John Henderson
      - Nassif, Ronald Floyd
      - North, William Harrison "Bill"
      - Reith, Charles C.
      - Robles, David Neal "Dave" Jr.
      - Rorick, Marvin H. "Marv"
      - Simmons, Douglas J., Jr. "Chip"
      - Smith, Stephen H. "Steve"
      - Umpleby, Michael Scott "Mike"
      - Trimble, Thomas Hart "Hart"
      - Valade, Christopher Carhartt "Chris" (includes Mark Robert) (1963-1965)
      - Wehle, J. Kent "Kent" (includes James A. "Jim") (1963-1964)
      - Weiss, Douglas Arthur "Doug"
      - Wiesel, Tom
    - 1964
      [Restricted until January 1 2064 ]
      - Abraham, Richard Arnold "Ricky" (Box 22)
      - Arbaugh, Steven Lee "Steve"
      - Beattie, Scott Mallon
      - Biedermann, Brent Taylor
      - Berlin, David Nelson "Dave"
      - Black, Coit A. (includes John D.)
      - Dye, Billy (includes David F. "Dave")
      - Field, Whitney K. "Whit"
      - Fowler, William Earl "Bill"
      - Glaenzer, Thomas Adams "Tom"
      - Gorman, Maurice P. (includes Mark J.)
      - Goss, Roger A. "Rog"
      - Gracie, William Harris "Chipper"
      - Griffin, Peter Raymond "Pete"
      - Hammond, Edmund James "Jim"
      - Harris, William W. "Billy"
      - Hoke, David Ault (includes Karl Humphreys)
      - Holmes, Jeffrey Alan "Jeff"
      - Knorr, Frederick August "Butch"
      - Mahoney, R. Michael "Mike" (Includes J. Patrick "Pat")
      - Mills, Steven Edward
      - Nutter, Robert Kennedy "Bob"
      - Rorick, Robert Baker "Rocky"
      - Schafer, Bruce Lee "Brucie" (includes Robert Samuel "Bobby" (1964-1965)
      - Sherbondy, David Edwin "Dave"
      - Stutt, James Valley "Jamie"
      - Tatum, Christopher Lee "Chris"
      - Wardwell, Jeffrey Holbrook "Jeff"
      - Winchester, Alan Weeks, Jr. "Wix"
    - 1965
      [Restricted until January 1 2065 ]
      - Anderson, Eric Worden (Box 23)
      - Athey, Robert L. "Bobby" (includes Brian David)
      - Bassett, Joseph D. Bassett "Joe" (includes Robert O. "Rob")
      - Batsch, Charles Warren "Chuck"
      - Binford, Wilson Clark "Bill"
      - Chilcote, Thomas Jones "Tommy"
      - Christman, Thomas Robert "Tom"
      - Corbridge, Charles Kelley "Kel" (includes Robert Scott "Scotty")
      - Dickey, Mathew "Mat"
      - Eurich, Donald
      - Field, Steven Alan "Steve"
      - Fitzgerald, Richard Michael "Mike"
      - Flannery, Michael Rogers "Mike"
      - Hall, Donald Andrew III "Andrew"
      - Harrison, Richard Lawrence "Dick"
      - Holiday, Harry III "Hap"
      - Jensen, James Crawford "Jim"
      - Mason, Horatio Pleasants "Pete"
      - Miller, Jonathon Paul
      - Moxley, Cameron "Cammy"
      - Phillips, David Chaffee "Dave"
      - Reilly, William Carlson "Billy" (includes Richard Cating "Richie") (1965-1966)
      - Richards, John W. "John"
      - Rosenberg, Jonathan "Jon"
      - Tucker, Lance Christopher "Butch"
      - Wallaert, Albert Jay "Beanie"
      - Weed, Cornelius C. III "Neal"
      - Woodward, James Hanna "Woody"
    - 1966
      [Restricted until January 1 2066 ]
      - Alzamora, Victor A. "Tito" (Box 23)
      - Beardsley, Charles Harold II "Chip"
      - Camp, David Lee "Dave"
      - Carroll, Charles H. "Chip"
      - Cavill, Bruce Dean
      - Christensen, James Robert "Jim"
      - Cobb, Brian Edward
      - Conaghan, Mark Thomas
      - Conibear, Michael "Mike"
      - deKam, Peter Fredrik
      - Dukay, Victor
      - Dyson, Alfred Leonard III "Chip" (includes David McDaniel "Dave")
      - Edwards, Stevenson L. "Steve" (includes Wade R.) (1964-1965)
      - Ely, Bartlett Spalding "Bart"
      - Garwood, Terry Anderson "Shades"
      - Gedrich, Daniel Michael "Dan"
      - Hall, Charles Louis "Charley"
      - Haugen, Mark Pell
      - Hickey, Michael Thomas "Mike"
      - Hopkins, William Robert "Bill" (includes Neil Colin)
      - Johnson, Scott William "Crusher"
      - Keeney, Timothy Val "Tim"
      - Moore, Dale Logan
      - Osler, Peter Lorch
      - Raymond, Randall James "Randy"
      - Schuman, Charles Lewis "Chuck"
      - Sharp, Jeffrey G. "Jeff"
      - Starrett, David Blake "Dave"
      - Templeton, Richard Scott "Scott"
      - Tomlin, John Grant "Grant"
      - Waldron, Scott Douglas
      - Wendahl, Eric Friend
    - 1967
      [Restricted until January 1 2067 ]
      - Andrews, Frank M. III, "Skip" (Box 23)
      - Ankenbruck, James Matthew "Matt"
      - Brown, John Randell (includes Peter Burke "Pete")
      - Cooley, Brad
      - Correil, Jonathan H. "Jon"
      - Cowing, James A. "Jim"
      - Drake, William D. "Chuck"
      - Early, Ellis Terrill III "Terry"
      - Ford, James W. "Jim"
      - Gust, Rockwell T. "Rocky"
      - Helm, David Leroy "Dave"
      - Helmke, Louis Edmund
      - Hodge, Arthur Wilton "Art"
      - Judge, Paul Cordiner
      - Katz, David Frank "Dave"
      - Kirkland, "Skip"
      - Lombard, David Carleton
      - Macartney, Grant Street
      - Marr, Richard A. "Ricky"
      - McKelvy, C. Lockhart "Lock"
      - Miller, Robert C. "Bob"
      - Murphy, Bill
      - Olson, David Lee "Dave" (includes Kent Roger)
      - Osler, Peter L. "Pete"
      - Peppel, Paul Karl
      - Petropoulos, John G.
      - Premo, Edward F. "Ed"
      - Reye, Gary George
      - Reynolds, Sherman Joseph
      - Rogge, William Fisher Jr., "Bill"
      - Schneider, Christopher Duane "Chris" (includes Mark Cowing)
      - Skakel, Rushton W. "Ricky"
      - Slotfeldt, Per
      - Stirling, Jamie
      - Storrs, John A.
      - Turner, William Ford "Bill"
      - Valade, Mark R.
      - Vaughn, Tad M. (includes Rex R.)
      - Weber, Mark Alexander
      - Weisman, Bruce Meyer
      - Wohlgemuth, Edward W. Jr. "Ted"
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1967 (Box 23)
    - Alumni Association Update Cards
  - Alphabetical File. 1925-1960
    - Acklin, Evan Callord (1938) (Box 23)
    - Allmand, Thomas Robert "Tommy" (1949)
    - Anderson, Pehr Denton (includes John Albin) (1945)
    - Ayres, Byron (1935)
    - Bandfield, David G. (1944)
    - Belser, Martin Fisk "Marty" (1942 1949)
    - Biggs, Raymond John "Ray" (includes Thomas William "Tom") (1946-1949)
    - Bird, Mrs. Iris (1947)
    - Bracken, Frank A. (1947)
    - Braheney, Thomas Jerome (1938)
    - Brigham, Brian P. (1949)
    - Bryan, Rodney "Rod" (1948-1949)
    - Bull, Richard (includes Robert) (1946)
    - Buszek, Beatrice R. (1947)
    - Butterfield, James (1946)
    - Card, Robert Watson "Robin" (1949)
    - Coan, Peter Gaylord (1946)
    - Copelin, Carl Brown "Brownie" (1944-1949)
    - Cost, John Joseph, Jr. (1945)
    - Courtis, William Stuart "Bill" (1947-1949)
    - Cress, George Henry (1944)
    - Cudlip, Robert Sherwood "Jack" (1934-1939)
    - Curtis, James Christie (1946)
    - Curtis, Charles (includes Philip) (1943-1944)
    - Davis, Thomas Eugene "Tom" (1949)
    - Dettlinger, Frederick W., Jr. (1946)
    - DeVore, Richard S. "Dick" (includes Robert William "Bob") (1949)
    - Doan, L. Alden (includes Herbert D. "Ted") (1929-1935)
    - Dobson, Rusty (1953) (Box 24)
    - Dobson, Stephen Boyd "Steve" (includes Peter MacLaunn) (1958-1960)
    - Douglas, Donald O. II (1944)
    - Dreese, Richard Nadeau "Dick" (1938-1939)
    - Dryden, George Eastman, Jr. (1938-1942)
    - Durst, Raymond (1944)
    - Ehman, Thomas F. "Tom" (1948-1949)
    - Elliott, Richard (1935-1936)
    - Fischer, Patrick Carl (1946)
    - Flesh, Alexander Smith (1938-1943)
    - Foster, Lawrence T. "Larry" (1946-1949)
    - Gabel, Norman W. (1946)
    - Garvey, Robert Arthur (1938-1939)
    - Giannestras, James Duncan "Jim" (1947-1949)
    - Goodwillie, Scott (deceased) (1928)
    - Gundrum, Frederick "Skipper" (1948-1949)
    - Hars, Ritz (1938-1942)
    - Herman, Donald Allen "Don" (1948-1949)
    - Higgins, Linnaes Boyd (1935-1947)
    - Hooper, Joe (1942)
    - Houck, Lawrence B. (1946-1950)
    - Igleheart, Edgar, Jr. (1934)
    - Irish, Jim (1953)
    - Irvin, Charles E. (1945-1946)
    - Jelliffe, Jack Hare (1938-1945)
    - Keely, Billy M. (1946)
    - Kern, Ernst Frederick, Jr. (Fritz) (1949)
    - Kirstein, Bob (1928)
    - Kretzschmar, Bob (1942)
    - Landen, Joseph D. (1938-1942)
    - Lathrop, Walter William, Jr. (1945)
    - Leckie, Major G. (1946)
    - Lighty, Jack D. (1942-1949)
    - Lyons, Laurance Alden (1945)
    - Mackey, Thomas Abbott (1946-1951)
    - Malcolm, Peter (includes James) (1946)
    - Marin, Edwin Woodruff (1948-1954)
    - Marquette, Eugene Oakleigh III (1947-1951)
    - Marquette, Joseph Chartrand (1948-1949)
    - Marr, Richard Austin (includes Walter Durant) (1940-1952)
    - Matuszewski, Edward (1948-1952)
    - Milburn, Joseph Andrews "Joe" (1945-1949)
    - Miller, George William (includes James Mann, Jr.) (1944-1950)
    - Moore, Joseph Edward "Joe" (1948-1949)
    - Mott, Stewart R. "Stew" (1949)
    - Mumma, Roger K. "Rog" (1948-1949)
    - Newberry, Charles Milton (1938-1939)
    - Nielsen, Philip P. "Phil" (1946-1949)
    - Nilsen, Christopher "Chris" (includes Nicholas "Nick") (1946-1949)
    - Noble, Bruce Jack (1943-1945)
    - Nolan, John Jeremiah "Jerry" (1938-1943)
    - Nolan, Robert Leslie (1938)
    - Palmer, Nathan H. (includes Bradley H.) (1946)
    - Paulson, Peter Joseph (includes LeRoy Thomas) (1945-1947)
    - Pierce, Richard (1946)
    - Pilliod, Thomas Jack (1945-1946)
    - Ratliff, Berry (1955)
    - Raymond, John Stowell (1947)
    - Reed, Dan Dwight (1948-1949)
    - Richardson, Ross C. (1948-1949)
    - Roth, Philip James M. (1944)
    - Sawicki, Ralph (1948-1953)
    - Scher, Stephen (1947-1948)
    - Schively, Nicholson Roots "Nick" (1938-1939)
    - Schott, Kenneth Crittenden (1945)
    - Seacrest, Jimmie (1947)
    - Severs, Roy M. (1946)
    - Silkworth, Donald (1947-1953)
    - Stienon, Francis Michael (includes Julian Peter) (1947-1950)
    - Strickler, William J. "Billy" (1949)
    - Stroh, Edwin R. III "Bill" (includes Peter B.) (1958-1959)
    - Talbot, Gerald J. (includes George-cousin) (1946)
    - Telfer, G. Thomas (1948)
    - Tieteg, Larry (1956)
    - Tolfree, Daniel Eugene (1944)
    - Tomblin, Gale Edward (1947-1949)
    - Twining, William F. "Bill" (1939)
    - VanderVeen, John David "Dave" (1947-1949)
    - Vos, John F. (1948-1954)
    - Wagner, Albert W. "Sandy" (1944)
    - Warren, John (includes Pat) (1948)
    - Weber, Tom W. (includes Carl R.) (1946-1953)
    - White, Benjamin Baily, III (1947)
    - Whitman, Peter Depew "Pete" (1945-1949)
    - Willertz, Frederick "Freddy" (1948-1951)
    - Williams, John Russell (1944-1952)
    - Yaryan, John Sturges, Jr. (1944-1948)
- Staff / Counselors files
  - Alphabetical 1925-1959
    - Albert, Dr. & Mrs. Richard & Catherine (1948) (Box 25)
    - Allison, Paul (1927)
    - Anderson, Mr. Louis J. (1931-1933)
    - Andrews, Tom (1945)
    - Barrett, David Joseph (1949)
    - Baske, Dr. Franklin W. (1929)
    - Beal, Mr. Robert (1930)
    - Beierlein, Dr. Karl (1926)
    - Bennett, Mr. Dick (1926-1927)
    - Benson, John (1936)
    - Berndt, Mr. Arnold W. (1929)
    - Binford, Tom, Junior Counselor, (1941)
    - Bittinger, Mr. Ross T. (1928-1932)
    - Blake, Forrester (1935)
    - Blocksma, Douglas (1939)
    - Blomfield, Lloyd (1935)
    - Boden, Mr. Marshall (1928)
    - Boehringer, Mr. Albert (1926)
    - Braidwood, Van (1945)
    - Brashares, Charles Merrill (1937)
    - Browne, Dr. Trevor G. (1926-1931)
    - Bryan, Christy A. (1947)
    - Bryan, Don (1948)
    - Bryan, Taylor (1946)
    - Bryant, Jim (1941)
    - Buchanan, Mr. Walter (1931)
    - Buckmaster, Clifford (1943)
    - Burow, George E. (1941)
    - Buszek, Ted C. (1947)
    - Campbell, C. Marsh (1949)
    - Cantrill, Mr. Cecil, Jr. (1929-1930)
    - Carter, Mr. Clare "Newt" (1925-1931)
    - Cathcart, Dr. Edward (1928)
    - Chubb, Donald (1945)
    - Conlin, Mr. Joseph (1929-1932)
    - Coon, Jim (1947)
    - Cooper, Dr. Ralph (1940)
    - Cooper, Dr. Robert (1927)
    - Corbett, Mr. Thad (1928-1931)
    - Corrigan, Clare (1944)
    - Courville, Dr. Charles J. (1939)
    - Crandall, Frank, Jr. (1949)
    - Cunningham, Mr. C. Howard (1931)
    - Daniells, Mr. William (1930-1932)
    - Deacon, Wallace (1943)
    - Dennison, Ed (1945)